So then, you head out.
Right?
You hit that threshold
and you're like...
Skrrt!
'Cause you realize...
you did not paint your toenails.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
And you have an inner conflict
because one part of you
is like, "I am not hampered
by society's limitations
-of femininity."
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
"I am my personality,
not my appearance.
For Colored Girls
Who've Considered Suicide
When the Rainbow's Enuf."
The other part of you is like,
"Hmmm..."
(IN SING-SONG)
"These shits look prehistoric."
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
So you gotta come
to a compromise within yo'self.
And that compromise is...
to just paint the two
that are showing!
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
He got to earn that pinky toe!
Yes, it do!